

Contact

Address:

28A Kervil Ave, Te Atatu Peninsula, Auckland

Phone:

022 1635502

Email:

yoyo1535417168@gmail.com

Website:

https://aipiro.github.io

Languages

Mandarin English

Skill Highlights

Creative design
Detail-oriented
Clear communication
Highly organized
Innovative problem-solving

Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP, MySQL, Bootstrap

CMS Platform:WordPress

UI/UX Design: Photograph,Adobe XD/Sketch

Summary

Efficient professional with 3 years of experience and a proven knowledge of web design, development and testing, specializing in front end. Computer Science degree, great communication skills, well-developed technological expertise. Aspiring to leverage my skills to successfully fill the role at your company.

Experience

Web Developer - Feb 2020 to Sep 2020(part time)
- July 2018 to Feb 2020 (full time)

New Zealand Express Travel Ltd

- Developed fully functional responsive website based on Business Requirements using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Performed designer roles to create well-designed interfaces and intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for websites and carry out quality assurance test.
- Daily update and maintenance website and providing guidance and troubleshooting support

Web Administrator - July 2017 to July 2018 New Zealand Express Travel Ltd

- Manage company official web environment design, deployment and maintenance activities for promoting business line.
- Proficient in using WordPress platform

Inter - July 2016 to July 2017

Rainbow in-Sign Co. Ltd

- Designing, developing and modifying a website, responsible for main web design task, the creation of page layouts, website styling and page features.
- Collaborate with team members completing the programming and development tasks.

Education

Auckland University of Technology (July 2014 – July 2017)

Degree: Bachelor of Computer and Information Science